RAMANDEEP KAUR

CUSTOMER CARE ASSOCIATE

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working recent college graduate with a Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Digital Media Communications (3.5 GPA), with 8 years of work experience. Aiming to leverage academic experience and a proven knowledge of Conflict resolution and customer needs assessment to successfully fill the customer care associate role at your company.

EXPERIENCE

FINANCIAL ASSISTANT

BP Oil , 11418, NY / Mar 2017 - Aug 2019

- Ensured data accuracy and reconciliation to financial systems.
- Prepared monthly financial reporting packages for internal management review.
- Booked journal entries and prepared account analyses.
- Handled billing and payment for the company.

BEAUTY SPECIALIST

Tom Ford, Manhattan, NY / Oct 2015 - Feb 2017

- Created personalized, lasting, positive and inviting impression for each customer.
- Executed store opening and closing procedures and recovery.
- Drove top line store sales results and growing business through action and productivity.
- Achieved sales goals while displaying prompt, courteous, knowledgeable and professional customer service.
- Met customer needs based on their personal requirements.

BEAUTY ADVISOR

Clinique Beauty, Queens, NY / Jul 2014 - Sep 2015

- Greeted all walk-in customers promptly delivering friendly and attentive service.
- Handled each transaction efficiently and accurately.
- Provided efficient and courteous services to clients based on their needs.
- Met sales and credit goals for the day.

FRONT DESK RECEPTIONIST

SUNY Downstate Medical Center, Brooklyn, NY / Sep 2012 - Jun 2014

- Scheduled patient appointments, answers phones and schedules referrals.
- Facilitated efficient and timely entry of patient to office setting.
- Sorted mail and packages and notified appropriate staff of

- ramandeep.patwar94@gmail. com
- (718) 269-8341
- **♀** 31717 Sedgefield Oval, Solon, OH, 44139

EDUCATION

BARUCH COLLEGE

GPA: 3.5 New York, NY

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) Digital Media Communications (Aug 2020)

Awards & Honors

- Magna Cum Laude
- National Honor Society
- Salutatorian

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Proficient in Hindi, Urdu, Punjabi Proficient in Microsoft Office HTML CSS JavaScript deliveries.

- Greeted all guests and ensured exceptional customer service experience.
- Demonstrated organization skills, accuracy and attention to detail.